Guide to the Cynthia Macdonald Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Writing
  - Poetry
    - Individual Poems
      - The Difference between Appetite and Hunger (Box 4, Folder 160)
      - Differential Diagnosis (Box 4, Folder 161)
      - Difficult Revision (Box 4, Folder 162)
      - Dinner before the Blue Horizon (Box 4, Folder 163)
      - Direction (Box 4, Folder 164)
      - Disappearance of the Blue Ribbon Dog (Box 4, Folder 165)
      - Discomfiting the Absolute Splendor (Box 4, Folder 166)
      - Discourse Must Not Take the Place of Art (Box 4, Folder 167)
      - Disguise (Box 4, Folder 168)
      - Distinction for Clarence Major (Box 4, Folder 169)
      - Divining Rod (Box 4, Folder 170)
      - The Doctor (Box 4, Folder 171)
      - Domestications of Loss (Box 4, Folder 172)
      - The Double Brooder (Box 4, Folder 173)
      - Double Talk (Box 4, Folder 174)
      - A Double Villanelle for Two Murdered Girls and Their Town (Box 4, Folder 175)
      - The Dr. Dimity Poems (Box 4, Folder 176)
      - The Drawing Room (Box 4, Folder 177)
      - The Dreamer on the Stone Couch Dreams and Wakes (Box 4, Folder 178)
      - Driving Home: A Point (Box 4, Folder 179)
      - Driving on Weslayan (Box 4, Folder 180)
      - Driving with One Hand out the Window (Box 4, Folder 181)
      - The East River (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Easter 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - The Eating Beauty (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Eating Yourself Up (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - The Eel as the Letter E (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Eight for Luncheon (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - The Electric Bed (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Elegy for Donald Pugmire, Photographer (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Elegy for Hans (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - The Elements of a Leader (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Emperor (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Empty Barn in Fairlee, Vermont (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Endings (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - The English Bulldog (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Engraved Sympathy (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Envy of Old Husbands (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Equation (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - The Erythrophobic Man (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Escalator (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Essay on Rhyme (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - The Essentials (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Etching (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Eve Weaver’s Psychoanalysis (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Exchanges (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Expanded to the Absurd (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Extempore (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Fall Letter/Shell Sekiyu (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Falling (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - The Family from Yoe, Pennsylvania, in Front Royal, Virginia (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Family History (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - A Family of Dolls’ House Dolls (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - A Family Question (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Fashion Facets (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - The Fat Child’s Song (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Fault or Blame (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Fear Is a Thistle (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - February 14, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Fiction after the Middle Ages (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - The Fifty Second Hour (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Finding the Solution (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Finishing School (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - The First Day (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - The First Wish Poem (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Fish Locket (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Five Non-Japanese Poems from Japan (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Flasher (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - The Flasher Opened up His Fly (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - The Flasher: Sequin Pricks (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Flashpoint: A Love Poem (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - The Floor His Father Paced (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - For Scott (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Forest Fire (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - The Four Virginias (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Frank Blank’s Gains and Losses (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Friday Morning in Westport, Conn. (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Friends: A Confusing Tale (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - From Despair at Not Hearing to Despair at Hearing (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - The Fungi as the Letter F (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - General Jacqueminot (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - The General Manager as Baron Ochs (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - The General Manager of the Opera (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Genesis (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Gertrude, Amy, Others and Not Me (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Getting Oder [sic] (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Getting to the End (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Getting What You Need (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Ghazals (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - A Given (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - A Glimpse, a Glimmer (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Grace (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Graffitus for Grace (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Grandchildren (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - The Grandmother (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - The Great 14th Street Costume Company, Clarence Ernest Klister, Prop (Box 5, Folder 74)
      - A Green Tray in the Cafeteria (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - The Group Is Collecting Its Tears (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Guide to the Runes (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - Gust around the Corner (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - Happens Are Like a Child’s Face (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - A Happy Beginning (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - Hasidim (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Hearing of a Four-Continent Fact-Finding Trip on the Five O’clock News… May 4, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - A Heart Still (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Helicopter (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - The Helper (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Here Is the Church and Here Is Myron (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - His Eggs (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - Hogs and Sperm (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Holocaust (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - The Holy Man Walks through Fire (Box 5, Folder 90)
      - The Horns, Being Gelatinous, Provide a Great Deal of Protein (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - The Horns of Forgetfulness (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - Hot Pot (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - The Hotel as Waxworks (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - The Hour of Feeling (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - The Hourglass (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - The House of Produce (Box 5, Folder 97)
      - The Household Finch (Box 5, Folder 98)
      - Houston Letter to H (Box 5, Folder 99)
      - How I Became a Partial Quadriplegic (Box 5, Folder 100)
      - How Much Wood Could a Wood-Witch Cut? (Box 5, Folder 101)
      - How to Tattoo a Heart on His Chest (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - How William Solomon Invokes Free Will (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - How You Can Tell the Dancer from the Dance (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Howard Takes the Fifth (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Hungarian Bombshells – April 1981 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Hunt for the Poem (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - Husbandry (Box 5, Folder 108)
      - Hymn in a Bed of Amherst (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - I Am Trying to Remember (Box 5, Folder 110)
      - I Ask Your Help Straightforwardly (Box 5, Folder 111)
      - I Did Not See the Grottos near Biblos (Box 5, Folder 112)
      - I Have Just Burned the Leaf City (Box 5, Folder 113)
      - I in the Sense of We (Box 5, Folder 114)
      - I Keep Losing My Place (Box 5, Folder 115)
      - I Stopped to Watch the Bird (Box 5, Folder 116)
      - I Thought the Furniture Would Keep Itself (Box 5, Folder 117)
      - I Want the World to Freeze (Box 5, Folder 118)
      - I Will Candle You with Flowers (Box 5, Folder 119)
      - Ice Fishing (Box 5, Folder 120)
      - Idols (Box 5, Folder 121)
      - If Only (Box 5, Folder 122)
      - The Igloo (Box 5, Folder 123)
      - Immeasurable Differences (Box 5, Folder 124)
      - The Impossible May Be Possible (Box 5, Folder 125)
      - Imprisoned (Box 5, Folder 126)
      - An Improper Bostonian (Box 5, Folder 127)
      - In Albatross Latitudes (Box 5, Folder 128)
      - In Such an Unhappy Neighborhood, Carlos (Box 5, Folder 129)
      - In the International Cafeteria (Box 5, Folder 130)
      - In the Museum (Box 5, Folder 131)
      - In the Shed the Baby Poses (Box 5, Folder 132)
      - Indian Winter in Houston (Box 5, Folder 133)
      - An Inequitable Life (Box 5, Folder 134)
      - Infection/Infected Selection (Box 5, Folder 135)
      - Infirmities (Box 5, Folder 136)
      - Inheritance (Box 5, Folder 137)
      - Initials by Richard Howard (Box 5, Folder 138)
      - Innard Life (Box 5, Folder 139)
      - The Insatiable Baby (Box 5, Folder 140)
      - The Inside Story (Box 5, Folder 141)
      - Institution for the Sane (Box 5, Folder 142)
      - Instruction from Bly (Box 5, Folder 143)
      - Instructions Enclosed in a Present for [Jane?] (Box 5, Folder 144)
      - Instructions for Burial (Box 5, Folder 145)
      - Interregnum (Box 5, Folder 146)
      - Inventory (Box 5, Folder 147)
      - Investiture (Box 5, Folder 148)
      - Inviting (Objet D’Art II) (Box 5, Folder 149)
      - Isn’t It Amazing (Box 5, Folder 150)
      - January 1980 (Box 5, Folder 151)
      - Japanese Ceramics (Box 5, Folder 152)
      - Jason, from Whom I Am Apart and of Whom a Part (Box 5, Folder 153)
      - Jennifer Is My Heart (Box 5, Folder 154)
      - Jewish Chicken Examines the Difference between Heaven and Hell (Box 5, Folder 155)
      - The Jews Are Losing Their Violins (Box 5, Folder 156)
      - Job’s from God, Mine from Family (Box 5, Folder 157)
      - The Kilgore Rangerette Whose Life Was Ruined (Box 5, Folder 158)
      - The Kiss of His Younger Brother (Box 5, Folder 159)
      - Knock, Knock (Box 5, Folder 160)
      - Kurt Herbert Adler – the General Manager of the Opera (Box 5, Folder 161)
      - Ladybug (Box 5, Folder 162)
      - Landing near May Swenson’s (Box 5, Folder 163)
      - The Last House (Box 5, Folder 164)
      - Lasting (Box 5, Folder 165)
      - Late Bloomers (Box 5, Folder 166)
      - The Late Mother (Box 5, Folder 167)
      - The Leader (Box 5, Folder 168)
      - Leonardo’s Advice to Artists (Box 5, Folder 169)
      - Lest We Lose Our Edens (Box 5, Folder 170)
      - Letter to a Long-Dead Father (Box 5, Folder 171)
      - Letter to Richard from Budapest (Box 5, Folder 172)
      - Lies (Box 5, Folder 173)
      - Lightning (Box 5, Folder 174)
      - Like a Chicken (Box 5, Folder 175)
      - Lila’s Mother Speaks to a Friend (Box 5, Folder 176)
      - Limits (Box 5, Folder 177)
      - Linked with Susan (Box 5, Folder 178)
      - The Lion, the Tiger and the Acorn (Mr.) (Box 5, Folder 179)
      - Little Gods (Box 5, Folder 180)
      - Little Grains of Sand Make a Might Ocean (Box 5, Folder 181)
      - The Lobster (Box 5, Folder 182)
      - Long Distance (Box 5, Folder 183)
      - Longing for the Indefinable Idea (Box 5, Folder 184)
      - Looking into My Father’s House (Box 5, Folder 185)
      - Louise (Box 5, Folder 186)
      - Love in Late Middle Age (Box 5, Folder 187)
      - Love Is Not a Censor (Box 5, Folder 188)
      - Love Letter to Mr. Moog (Box 5, Folder 189)
      - Love Poem to a Woman (Box 5, Folder 190)
      - The Loved One’s Lament (Box 5, Folder 191)
      - A Lovely Dinner (Box 5, Folder 192)
      - Lover (Box 5, Folder 193)
      - Lovers (Box 5, Folder 194)
      - The Lovesong of Chicken Athena (Box 5, Folder 195)
      - Lucy, Driving with One Hand out the Window (Box 5, Folder 196)
      - A Lullabye for Big One (Box 5, Folder 197)
      - Magnitude (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Making It (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Making Love in front of the Doll’s House (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - The Man Who Lives in the Room (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - The Man Who Writes on Air (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Manning Park – Five Years after the Fire (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Many Japan Holdouts Said Hiding in Islands (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - The Many Truths of RG (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Maps and Globes (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Marathon (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - March 77 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Marriage Song – June 20, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - The Marschallin Gives a Voice Lesson (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Mary Shelley (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Mary’s Lament (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - The Mass Murderer (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Maybe a Mountain Lion/A Cougar (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Meeting Norberto Chiesa (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - The Memorial (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Mendelssohn’s Second Symphony (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Message to Our Leader (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Microcosm (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - The Midget as Joy (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Midwife (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Millennium Riddle (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Miriam’s Grandmother (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Mistress Mary Quite Contrary (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Mme. Sybil Willoughby Tells the City’s Fortune (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Mondrian I & II (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - The Mongols (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Moons on the Bus (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - More Perilous than Worm (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - The Morning of Armageddon (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Mornings with Mummy (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - The Mosaic Hunchback (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Mother and Child (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Mother and Daughter (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Mother Earth in Challenger Seven Park (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - The Mother of the Sun (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - The Mother Suite (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Moving Portrait of the Painter’s Father (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - A Moving Present for EG (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Mud (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - The Murderer’s Daughter: Inside and Outside (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - Musee d’Orsay: Les Dindons (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - The Museum (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - Museum Dedication (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - Museums (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - Music Transforms a Day (Box 6, Folder 49)
      - Mutations (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - My Birthday (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - My Familiar Lover (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - My Mind Is a Spangled Fritillary (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - My Unfamiliar Lover (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Narcissa in Newfoundland (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Nashville Song Waiting for Country Music (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - The Natural History Museum at Night (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Navery (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Needed: More Room (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - The Needling Witch (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Negation (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - New England Story (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - News of the Death of the World’s Biggest Man (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - Night’s Music (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - No Appeal (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - No One Told Me You Were Beautiful (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Not to Be Remembered (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Note to a Student (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - The Nurturing Mother (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Objets D’Arts (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Oddly Destined (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Oil for the Lamps of China (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Old Age (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Old Woman Bed-Bound (Box 6, Folder 74)
      - On Forgetting to Check What Needs to Be Checked (Box 6, Folder 75)
      - On Learning of a Friend’s Illness (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - On Navajo Sands (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - On Seeing the Posthumous Masterpiece (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - On Stages of Suffering (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - On the Sideboard, Three Candles (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - On Your Somnambulism (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Once You Notice Chickens They Are Everywhere (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - One (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - One in a Velvet Gown (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - The One Who Did Not Die (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - The Opera House (Box 6, Folder 86)
      - Opposition: None (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - The Order of the Visitation (Box 6, Folder 88)
      - Orpheus or Lot as Midas (Box 6, Folder 89)
      - Other Uses (Box 6, Folder 90)
      - The Outcome of a Leader (Box 6, Folder 91)
      - Outwitting the Oceanic (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - Overnighters (Box 6, Folder 93)
      - P.T. Barnum (Box 6, Folder 94)
      - A Painter’s Poem (Box 6, Folder 95)
      - Paintings from the Slaughterhouse: A Slide Show of Hogs (Box 6, Folder 96)
      - Panygyric with Pigeons (Box 6, Folder 97)
      - The Parfit Gentil Dodo (Box 6, Folder 98)
      - Pas de Deux (Box 6, Folder 99)
      - Passover (Box 6, Folder 100)
      - A Past-Due Notice (Box 6, Folder 101)
      - Past Ordering (Box 6, Folder 102)
      - Patient – Female – 81 (Box 6, Folder 103)
      - Pearl Onion (Box 6, Folder 104)
      - Perfect Adjustment (Box 6, Folder 105)
      - A Perfect Binding (Box 6, Folder 106)
      - Perfection Escapes Me: Pursue, Pursue (Box 6, Folder 107)
      - Perspective (Box 6, Folder 108)
      - Peter (Box 6, Folder 109)
      - Phases of Love (Box 6, Folder 110)
      - Photography (Box 6, Folder 111)
      - The Pieces of My Life (Box 6, Folder 112)
      - Piranesi’s Pirandello (Box 6, Folder 113)
      - A Place to Watch the Birds (Box 6, Folder 114)
      - The Plague at Eyem: 1666 A.D. (Box 6, Folder 115)
      - A Plague of Fleas (Box 6, Folder 116)
      - The Platform Builder (Box 6, Folder 117)
      - The Plumber (Box 6, Folder 118)
      - Po’ Chicken Views the Moon (Box 6, Folder 119)
      - A Pocket Full of Posies (Box 6, Folder 120)
      - The Poem as Fish (Box 6, Folder 121)
      - Poem for Ann (Box 6, Folder 122)
      - Poem(s) of Sweetness and Light to Counteract a Tendency toward Bitterness and Gloom (Box 6, Folder 123)
      - Poet-Chicken Answers the Interviewer (Box 6, Folder 124)
      - The Poet Guys (Box 6, Folder 125)
      - Poetry Reading at the Y (Box 6, Folder 126)
      - The Poisoner (Box 6, Folder 127)
      - Pop Art – I (Box 6, Folder 128)
      - Pop Art – II (Box 6, Folder 129)
      - Portrait of a Friend (Box 6, Folder 130)
      - Possession (Box 6, Folder 131)
      - Postcard of Child Peeking out from under Its Mother’s Skirt (Box 6, Folder 132)
      - The Potters Wheel Is Sometimes a Rack (Box 6, Folder 133)
      - Prayer (Box 6, Folder 134)
      - Prayer for the Deserving (Box 6, Folder 135)
      - Prayer for the Deserving II (Box 6, Folder 136)
      - The Precise Shape of a Wave (Box 6, Folder 137)
      - The Presence of the Senses by the Absence of the Senses (Box 6, Folder 138)
      - The Present (Box 6, Folder 139)
      - The Presents (Box 6, Folder 140)
      - Pres. Nixon’s Day: The 7 O’clock News, Jan. 30, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - The Priest Poet (Box 6, Folder 142)
      - Prints from Tokyo (Box 6, Folder 143)
      - Private Poem for Bill (Box 6, Folder 144)
      - Private Poem for Dr. Hirt (Box 6, Folder 145)
      - Prizes (Box 6, Folder 146)
      - A Profusion of [Ties?] (Box 6, Folder 147)
      - The Proof of Age (Box 6, Folder 148)
      - Proven (Box 6, Folder 149)
      - Psychoanalysis: A Flashlight (Box 6, Folder 150)
      - Pull (Box 6, Folder 151)
      - The Pull of Despair (Box 6, Folder 152)
      - Puzzle (Box 6, Folder 153)
      - The Puzzle Piece (Box 6, Folder 154)
      - The Queen (Box 6, Folder 155)
      - The Question of Why (Box 6, Folder 156)
      - Rain Is Committed (Box 6, Folder 157)
      - Rainy Day (Box 6, Folder 158)
      - Ramirez Poem (Box 6, Folder 159)
      - Rapacinni’s Daughter (Box 6, Folder 160)
      - Reading Condolence Letters (Box 6, Folder 161)
      - Reading House of Glass on the Noon Train – Westport-Grand Central (Box 6, Folder 162)
      - Rebecca Clearman’s Unconscious Decided to Cancel Again (Box 6, Folder 163)
      - Recycling (Box 6, Folder 164)
      - Red Cap and the Suitcases (Box 6, Folder 165)
      - Refilling the Stapler (Box 6, Folder 166)
      - Reflected Light (Box 6, Folder 167)
      - Reflections in Stone (Box 6, Folder 168)
      - Refusing Further Risk (Box 6, Folder 169)
      - Remains (Box 6, Folder 170)
      - Remains – Stratigraphy (Box 6, Folder 171)
      - Remembering Names (Box 6, Folder 172)
      - Renee Fleming Sings Marguerite: Gounod’s Faust (Box 6, Folder 173)
      - Repetition: Eight for Dinner (Box 6, Folder 174)
      - Reply to the Request from the Remaining Poet for Suicide Suggestions (Box 6, Folder 175)
      - Residence in the Saugatuck, P.O. (Box 6, Folder 176)
      - Retrieval (Box 6, Folder 177)
      - The Return of Feeling: 1937-1977 (Box 6, Folder 178)
      - Return of the Dream (Box 6, Folder 179)
      - Rewards (Box 6, Folder 180)
      - Richard’s Book and Chopper Ganz (Box 6, Folder 181)
      - Riddle (Box 6, Folder 182)
      - The River Honey Queen Bess (Box 6, Folder 183)
      - Robert Underhill’s Present (Box 6, Folder 184)
      - Sad Heart at the Bookstore (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Sales Talk (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Satan in Yugoslavia (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - A Satisfactory Poem (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - The Scale (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Scatter Bodies (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Scavengers (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Scoring “The Devil’s Trill” (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Sculpture: A Translation (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Searchlight (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - The Secrets of E. Munch (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Self-Pity (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - The Sensual and Moral Effects of Color (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Separations (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Serial Rescue (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - A Series of Poems for a Man Too Lazy to Write (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Sestina (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Settling (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - The Seven Stages of Mourning (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - The Shark Grows Hungrier (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Shields (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Shiva Dances Holding Juicy Orbs in Her Many Hands (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Shore Time (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Show and Tell (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - The Siamese Sextuplets (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Signalling (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Simon Says (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Singing Miriam’s Lament (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - The Singing Teacher (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Sisters (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Sitting in My Tokyo House, I Turn (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Six Feet in the Grave (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - The Skating Rink (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - The Skinny (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - A Slide Show of Hogs (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Slight of Sight (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - The Slopes of Parnassus (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - A Small Part of Charlene Hunter (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - The Snow Queen (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Something Shared (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Somewhere over the Rainbow (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Song of an Old Recluse (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - The Space of a Sister (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Spearville, Kansas (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Spelling It Out (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Spiders and Fat (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Spinning (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - The Spook House (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Spring Blizzard (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Sp(ring) Chicken (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Spring Pattern (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - A Squirrel on the Fence (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - The Stained Glass Woman (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Stanley Kunitz (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - A Step by Step Guide (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - A Step toward Burial (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - The Sting (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - The Story of My Detached Retina and Its Effects (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - Strange, the Occasion When Suddenly (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - The Stuff of Dreams (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Subsequently (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Suburban Soothsayer (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Succession (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - Succor (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - Succotash (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - The Sugar Lump (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Summer in Lake Placid (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Summer Letter (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Summer Storm from an Apartment on Central Park West (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - The Sun Maid Raisin Girl (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Supplanting the Beloved (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Surrogate (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Survival (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Susan Crile Dreams (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Taking the Car to Sears Automotive Center (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Tent Caterpillars Hang Heavy (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - The Terminal (Box 7, Folder 77)